saveupcash.com 2010-01-02

# SaveUpCash – Online Shopping with Cash Back and Coupons

This web site is created, owned and operated by SaveUpCash.com. We take user privacy seriously and make reasonable efforts to protect your privacy. We have created this Privacy Policy in order to share with you our information collection and use practices to making this site a success for us and our members. This policy applies solely to information collected at www.SaveUpCash.com. 

**Personal Data Collection**  
Only User's email address is collected when users make registration to SaveUpCash.com. User's email is also collected when users intentionally input email address to the email subscription box which allows user to subscribe our newsletter services. In order to use certain portions of the services, however, you may be asked for, or you may choose to provide, certain personal information such as name, phone number, PayPal account and similar information. We will not collect your personal information while you use the services unless you provide us or authorize us to collect such information voluntarily. 

**Non-personal Data Collection**  
SaveUpCash collects and tracks certain non-personal information such as user's IP address, browser type, access times, usage habits and other information which does not specifically identify any individual. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Our servers log your IP address for the purposes of web traffic analysis and trends. 

**Use of Personal Data**  
The information we collect will be analyzed for making relevant and personalized offers to our members based on their browsing or purchasing history. We will not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources. As with any other information that you supply to SaveUpCash, none of the information that we collect will be released in any personally identifiable way. 

**Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are small text files that store messages to a web browser by a web server. The message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. The main purpose of cookies is to identify users and possibly prepare customized web pages for them. So we may use cookies to identify you and allow you to log in once to SaveUpCash and shop without having to log in again. Cookies are also used by many of our merchants in order to identify you as a member of SaveUpCash and these cookies are not subject to SaveUpCash's privacy policies. 

**Children and Privacy**  
SaveUpCash always encourages parents and guardians to spend time with their children when surfing in the Internet and thoroughly familiar with the sites visited by their children. 

We do not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information. No information should be submitted to or posted on SaveUpCash by users under the age of 13 years without the permission of their parents and guardians. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. User should notify this Privacy Policy if there are any changes posted by SaveUpCash. 

**Unsubscribe Procedures**  
To unsubscribe the newsletter services from a particular list, follow the instructions in each promotional email message sent by SaveUpCash.com.
